maritimesun.com 2011-11-08

# Privacy Statement - MaritimeSun | MaritimeSun

Last update: August, 2010

NK [Maritime]( "Maritime") Sun Ltd is firmly committed to the protection of your privacy. This Statement sets out how we collect, use and secure the personal information of individuals in our Site.

BY USING shippingworld.maritimesun.com SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS STATEMENT, DISCONTINUE ALL USE OF THIS SITE IMMEDIATELY.

**What is “Personal Information”?**

Personal information is information about you that uniquely identifies you as an individual. Your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number are all examples of personal information. However, the name, address and telephone number of an individual that appears in a telephone directory that is available to the public (where such individual can refuse to have such information appears in such directory) does not fall under the scope of “personal information as it is publicly available information. Also, in some circumstances, some of this information may qualify as business information which is not covered by this Statement.

**Collection of Personal Information**

We do not automatically gather any personal information from users of shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site. Personal information is only obtained online if you supply it voluntarily, usually through contacting us via e-mail, applying online, answering online surveys, submitting a posting to a blog, forum, or review or registering for services. You are not required to supply personal information to view the content of shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site. You should also be aware that when you share personal information in public areas of shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site, this information may be seen and used by others users. We urge you to exercise good judgment when sharing personal information in these areas.

If you decide not to provide us with personal information online, no material consequences will result, although you may be unable to participate in certain promotions, receive product information, or use portions of shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site that require personalized information. shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request contact information about you.

shippingworld.maritimesun.com site may use cookies to track user traffic patterns. A cookie is a small data file that certain sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data from your hard disk or cookie files created by other sites. shippingworld.maritimesun.com does not correlate this information with data about individual users, nor does it share this information or sell it to any third party. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser.

We may use software that receives and records the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer that has contacted shippingworld.maritimesun.com site. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting shippingworld.maritimesun.com site.

We may also use third party’s advertisements on shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site or shippingworld.maritimesun.com advertisements on other sites. In serving advertisements these providers may place cookies on your browser computer and may collect certain anonymous information about your visits to other sites or on shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site. This information may include browser type, IP address, domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered such sites, web activity and time of day. This information is used by these third parties to better understand and optimize the online advertising campaigns.

From time to time, we analyze traffic and use shippingworld.maritimesun.com site to determine which features and services people like and do not like so that we can improve what we do. We prepare aggregated user statistics or information summaries in order to describe our services to third parties such as prospective business partners and advertisers and for other lawful purposes.

**Use and Sharing of Personal Information**

We will generally collect and use personal information to administer our contests, promotions, surveys, reward programs and other services, to understand our customers’ responses, needs and preferences, and to generally manage our business.

We may also use personal information to contact our customers or suppliers with marketing or promotional materials regarding our products, programs and services or to assist our front-line staff in providing tailored sales offers to our customers. We may exchange or merge personal information with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes.

**Your Consent**

By providing us with your personal information, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of that information as described in this Statement as amended from time to time or as described at or before the time of collection, use or disclosure, as the case may be. If you do not want your personal information to be collected, used or disclosed in this manner, then please either:

* do not submit your personal information to us;

* exercise opt-out procedures described above or as may be offered at the time of collection, or

* refrain from exercising opt-in procedures described above or as may be offered at the time of collection.

If you have submitted personal information to us and wish to withdraw your consent to its retention, use or disclosure, please send an e-mail to marketing@maritimesun.com. You may withdraw your consent, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide some products or services to you.

Where permitted or required by law, we may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent, for example, to collect a debt you owe us, to comply with a legally permitted inquiry by a government agency, or to comply with a court order.

**Safeguards and Retention**

We use physical, organizational and technological safeguards to protect your personal information against theft, loss or unauthorized access, use, modification, disclosure or disposal. Generally speaking, you can visit shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site without revealing personal information. However, given that electronically submitted data is not 100% secure, we make no warranties as to the security of any personal information you submit online, which you do at your own risk.

**Terms of Use & Changes to this Statement**

Your use of shippingworld.maritimesun.com Site, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Statement and governed by our Terms of Use, including its choice of law provisions. We reserve the right to change and update the Policy and these changes will be made when appropriate, in a timely manner. We encourage you to examine our Policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes we may have made.

**Access and Contact**

Upon written request, shippingworld.maritimesun.com will provide you access to your personal information, subject to certain exceptions as provided by the applicable legislation. If you notice any errors or omissions in your personal information, please advise us in writing and we will promptly correct them where appropriate. If you have concerns regarding our Statement, the security of your personal information or our compliance with the applicable personal information protection legislation, please send a brief explanation of your concern at: marketing@maritimesun.com
